[A Bona Fide Killer]
[This is a fictional story. All characters
and events bear no relation to reality]
[Child and animal scenes filmed safely]
[under the guardian
and expert supervision per guidelines]
[The Salvation Army Red Kettle]
Merry Christmas!
Do you want subtitles for any video?
-=[ ai.OpenSubtitles.com ]=-
What is it?
Ji Ah. I got you a present.
Wow! A teddy bear!
Thank you so much. Daddy!
It's been seven years
since I last saw your face.
I've missed you so much all that time.
More than anything.
I'm sorry for leaving you all alone.
I've blamed myself every single day.
That day...
I shouldn't have done that that day.
I think something got into it.
I'll get you another one.
You turned out so well. my daughter.
Now that I see you.
you look just like your late mom.
For seven years in prison.
I stared at the ceiling every night.
filled with regret.
That day...
I should've killed you too.
- Let go!
- You ungrateful brat!
After everything I did for you.
you reported your own dad?
Do you have any idea how long
I've been waiting for this day?
You little...
You brat.
Where do you think you're going?
I'll finish what I should've done back then.
You little brat.
Get over here. Get over here!
Stay still. you punk.
The more you struggle.
the harder it'll be on you.
Relax...
It's time for you to go meet your mom too.
[Machine Wash]
[Merry Christmas]
Do you want a Christmas present?
Then no crying.
You have to be good.
I heard that Santa is very clear
about right and wrong.
Miss. who are you?
Leave the living room window
slightly open when you get home.
And leave the lights on.
See you again.
[15 Years Later. Present Day]
Mommy. wake up!
Yul. you're awake?
Daddy. wake up too!
Five more minutes. just five...
No. you have to go to work!
Yul really takes after you.
no doubt about it.
Jeez. she's listening.
My Yul. you're so smart
because you take after your daddy.
Are you awake?
Really?
Are you so smart
because you take after me. Yul?
Yul. come here!
Daddy. get up already.
Oh. my little precious. Come here.
Yul. did you sleep well?
I think we put her to bed too early.
Well. who was it that insisted
on putting her to bed so early?
Was that me?
Then our big precious too...
I need to go potty.
- Potty...
- Let's go potty.
Come on. Let's go potty.
Let's go! Let's go potty.
[Episode 1]
The monster's coming after you!
I'll catch you!
Let's go! Yul. let's go! Come on!
[Kwon Yul. Dad. Mom]
All done! Let's go!
Daddy! The swings!
The swings!
Well. it's good. right?
Four-year-olds can eat on their own. right?
Yeah.
Go ahead. Yul. Try eating by yourself.
Time for an important decision.
The selfish new look. bought with money
stashed away from my wife.
Or the rebellious night out. lying about
working late and heading to the club.
Which one?
The rebel look today?
Oh. my! Really?
Wow. my wife is so generous.
When was the last time I went clubbing?
Yul. did you eat it all by yourself?
Awesome! You can eat all by yourself now!
Daddy! Yul finished all her food.
Really? You ate it all by yourself?
That's amazing. my girl!
What time is it? Oh. time to get dressed.
Let's go!
Let's go. let's go! Let's get you changed.
Honey. her P.E. uniform is over there.
Yul. do you have P.E. today?
- Yeah.
- That's nice.
- What time is it?
- Okay. then.
stand on one foot for five seconds.
Start!
One. two. three. four. five!
Success!
- Success!
- One. two. three!
- One more time. One. two. three!
Have fun with your friends. See you tonight!
- Okay! Bye-bye!
- Bye-bye!
Here.
What?
I feel like I had an important reason
to get off work early today.
What was it?
Seriously. what was it?
Well. what could it be?
You're not falling for it. huh?
I'll be home early today.
For my honey's big day tomorrow.
Oh. stop it.
But if you'd forgotten.
you would've been in big trouble.
I really hope not.
Right.
Ms. Yoo Bo Na. have a great day today.
And I'll see you this evening.
Alright.
What about what we didn't do earlier?
Now!
I'll get going. Bye-bye.
- Bye!
- Me too!
A kiss for Yul too!
A kiss for Yul too! Bye!
Bye-bye!
- See you later.
- Have a good day!
- I'll get going.
- Yul. I'm closing the door.
♪ Baby shark. doo. doo. doo. doo ♪
♪ Yul shark. doo. doo. doo. doo ♪
♪ Mommy shark. doo. doo. doo. doo ♪
♪ Daddy shark. doo. doo. doo. doo ♪
♪ Grandma ♪
♪ Doo. doo. doo. doo ♪
Yul. shall we sing the song again?
♪ Daddy shark. doo. doo. doo. doo ♪
Yes. yes. Don't run! Be careful. careful!
- Goodbye!
- Yeah. yeah.
Take care.
Seo Jun!
Up you go.
Please take good care of him today.
Be sure to listen to your teacher. okay?
- I'll be off.
- Okay. have a good day. Ma'am.
- Hello!
Hello.
Hello!
- Hello.
- Hello!
She always looks so relaxed. It's nice.
- Yul. you're here!
- Hello.
Miss. I ate breakfast all by myself today.
Oh. really? You did a great job.
Yul. say hello to your teacher first.
- Give her a nice big bow.
- Good morning.
Please take good care of her today too.
Don't worry. Yul seems to have adjusted now.
Totally different from the beginning.
she's playing well and doing great.
That's thanks to you. Thank you.
Yul. shall we say goodbye to Mommy today?
Okay. My Yul.
- Today. too. with friends.
- get along well!
- Have a nice day!
- Yul. let's go.
Have a good day. Ma'am. See you later.
- Okay.
- Yul's mom!
How about a morning coffee for a change?
That sounds great.
Oh. Ye Geon's mom.
did you not sleep well last night?
My kid dozed off poorly
in the early evening. woke up.
and then couldn't fall back asleep
until late at night.
- Oh. dear. really?
- See?
I told you. right?
That's why you need to
stick to a daily routine.
Otherwise. you'll end up twice as exhausted.
Look at me. No matter how tired I am.
I never let my kid nap during the day.
Right. naps...
By the way. isn't Seo Jun's mom amazing?
I saw earlier that she even seemed
to forget that today was P.E. day.
I don't know how she manages
to work while raising a child.
I'll... I'll go get it. You stay here.
How can you say that
after seeing that poor child earlier?
If you can't do both properly.
you should just focus on one thing.
Oh. dear.
I just feel sorry for her.
Oh. well.
Thank you!
The latte...
Still. I envy Seo Jun's mom sometimes.
It's hard. but at least
she gets to keep working.
I only planned to take a short break.
but sometimes I regret staying home.
Me too.
After spending all day dealing with my kid.
I sometimes miss working outside too.
Who wouldn't want to keep working?
Is there anyone here
who doesn't want to work?
That's why I call it being greedy.
Kids need so much attention at that age.
How can you leave them and work?
Is it really impossible?
Is it really that hard to work
while raising a child?
I really hope not...
Why?
I'm going back to work starting tomorrow.
Oh. my.
My parental leave ends today.
so I'm going back to work tomorrow...
Wait. you were a working mom this whole time?
How did we not know?
What. so you were just
taking a break from work?
How long were you off work?
- One year?
- Three years.
I wanted to wait until my child
was a little older before going back...
Three years? Are you a civil servant?
Or do you work for a major company?
No. I just work for a small company.
A small company.
Small...
I really enjoyed having
morning coffee together like this.
and learning parenting tips from you all.
And the coffee here is so delicious. right?
Today is D-Day. Soryong Nightclub. Musan.
Today? Why does it have to be today?
This won't do. This is a problem.
I'm really in trouble now. Oh. my.
Honey. I'm sorry. Really.
But this D-day was scheduled first...
I'll really make it up to you.
[Mother]
Mother? Yes.
Yeah. it's fine. Go ahead.
It must be a great company.
It's not easy to take the full three years
of parental leave.
Or maybe she's just really capable?
Well. she's been off for three years.
Why bother going back now...
I got it!
What is it?
The husband must be
struggling financially. I guess.
- Oh. no.
- That must have been hard.
She never told us.
Well. she has to earn her own money. I guess.
More than half of the drug cases
uncovered by police in recent months
have involved people in their 20s and 30s.
New types of drugs. including
liquid marijuana. ketamine. and fentanyl.
are reportedly spreading
among ordinary office workers and students
through clubs and private academies.
Mother. I'm here! Hello. Sister-in-law.
Oh. my. you're here. What brings you here?
I made some radish kimchi
that Tae Seong likes.
Oh. radish kimchi?
Let me get that. Mother. Just leave it.
Wow. it looks so appetizing
just from the sight of it.
My mom sure has all kinds of excuses
to call her daughter-in-law over.
Will my son even eat properly
starting tomorrow?
Don't worry. Mother.
I'll make sure he eats well.
No wonder you treat him
like your precious only son.
I'm sure she'll take good care of him.
These days. daughters-in-law don't really
like their mothers-in-law fussing over them.
Is that so?
No. Mother. I really appreciate it.
Thank you. Mother. We'll enjoy it.
No matter how busy I was.
I've never fed my family instant food.
I'll keep that in mind. Mother.
Speaking of which. Mother.
that soy-marinated crab. jellyfish salad.
and pickled perilla leaves
you made last time.
could you make them again?
- Huh?
- Tae Seong really loved them.
We finished them in less than three days.
Oh. sure. I'll make them.
Really? Thank you.
Is there anything
I can help you with. Mother?
Oh. no. just go quickly.
You probably have a lot to prepare.
- No. it's fine.
- Oh. my.
Why does my shoulder hurt so much today?
- When am I going to finish all this...
- Mother. leave it.
- I'll do it. Leave it.
- Mother!
Okay. let's do this.
Oh. Mom. really...
Do you really have to work her
on her last day off?
I'm not making her do anything.
She offered to do it.
Oh. dear.
- What?
- Oh. hello.
Is your daughter-in-law
going back to work tomorrow?
She's returning to work or something.
Oh! That's good.
It's hard to make a living on
one income these days.
My son has been working himself
to the bone supporting the family alone.
So. was she just sitting around
all this time?
Jeez. I'm sure her salary
is barely anything anyway.
She's already acting all high and mighty.
Mom!
When did she ever act like that?
Didn't you say your daughter-in-law
worked for some big company?
Was it some place
that sells refrigerators and TVs?
You're talking nonsense.
That one. She works for that fan company.
I need to replace my fan.
Can you get an employee discount
or something?
They probably don't make much money
selling those anyway.
Anyway. why are you here?
- Did you hear?
- Hear what?
That Chinese restaurant in the front
shopping area is closing down.
What? Isn't that the place
where people line up to eat?
Why are they suddenly closing?
Apparently the building owner
tripled the rent.
- Oh. my.
- What else could it mean?
They're telling them to leave.
Wow. that's really nasty.
Since business is good. they want to
open their own restaurant there.
[Tae Seong Chicken]
[Big sale today:
30% off select industrial products]
[50% off all agricultural products]
Oh. the mart is having a sale.
At least I've been lucky with my landlord.
The rent for all the shops around here
goes up every year.
but mine has stayed the same for five years.
It'll probably stay that way
this time too. right?
I guess so.
Oh! Oh. my gosh! You're being too naive.
How can you be so sure
about someone's intentions?
After five years frozen. they could raise it
all at once. and we'd have no say.
Oh. no way!
Business isn't even good these days.
If you're really worried.
you should visit the landlord beforehand
and show some appreciation.
Who could say no to a smiling face?
Sun Il. let's go buy a gift right now.
The landlord must be loaded.
What are you going to buy?
I guess you're right.
What should we buy. then?
Ask your daughter-in-law.
Young moms usually
have a better sense for these things.
What sense? My foot.
She showed up empty-handed
the first time she came to meet
her future mother-in-law.
One time. I asked her to buy
some red ginseng as a gift.
and she brought back
a whole fresh ginseng root instead.
Come on. no way!
My sister-in-law is just a little unusual.
Sometimes she just doesn't know things
everyone else does.
Really?
Well. that's probably
because she's an orphan.
She didn't have parents
to learn those things from.
Bye.
Oh. what do you mean help?
She couldn't even stick around and ran off...
When did she chop all of this?
Look at how even they are.
How can this...
I'm scared.
- What's this?
- What is going on?
[Black Beans]
Black beans...
[Today Only: Unbeatable Price.
50% Off All Agricultural Products]
- These onions are nice and big.
- They're so cheap.
- The autumn squash is a good price.
- Oh. my.
They're doing something over there too.
Let's go check it out.
Miss Kim!
What are you doing after work?
I asked what you're doing afterward.
Why are you acting like this?
Come on. just stay a minute.
You like this. don't you?
Please don't do this.
I'll get going now.
Who was that?
Miss Kim!
Oh. my back!
[Trash Can Deodorizer]
Who did this?
Who was it?
Oh. my.
Now. for the next 30 minutes only.
we're offering our seasonal
health-boosting samgyetang
at a special buy-one-get-one deal.
Got the samgyetang!
[Big Precious]
Honey. I love you!
I'll really make it up to you.
Wow. my wife really saw it coming.
[Musan Soryong Nightclub]
Wait. get out. Get out.
Come here. I need to wipe your feet.
No. I don't want to!
Yul. come here! You have to wipe your feet.
You'll catch a cold. Hurry.
Okay. Then stay right there.
Honey. I'm in Musan right now.
Something urgent came up
for a business trip. so I might be late.
I was supposed to get home early
and help you... I'm sorry.
I'll take the last bus and come.
even if I'm late.
I love you. Bo Na.
You know how much I love you. right?
Oh. this man. seriously...
Just wait until you get home.
You're not getting away with this.
It can't be helped. It's okay.
Take care of your work and don't worry.
Just stop sending those crying emojis.
Yul. let's get dressed now!
- Come here.
- No. I don't want to.
Come here!
- Come on. hurry.
- No!
Come quickly.
Come here! Come here!
Boss. I'll just go use
the bathroom real quick.
You punk!
I'm sorry.
Give it to me!
[Empty Taxi]
Follow that black car. please.
Let's sleep.
I'm going to sleep with Daddy.
When's Daddy coming?
I told you that Daddy is busy with work
and will be late today.
Sleep with me. okay?
No. I'll sleep when Daddy gets home.
Where did Daddy go?
His work isn't finished yet.
Should I sing you a song?
What kind of work?
Daddy is doing...
something very. very important.
He is a truly good man
who does wonderful things for people.
A good person?
Yes. A very good person
who makes the world brighter.
Yeah. honey.
Honey. are you on your way?
Yes. I'm on my way.
I prepared the barbecue.
but I haven't picked out the wine yet.
Barbecue with wine?
Of course. Napa Cabernet.
Napa Cabernet? Okay. I'll get that. then.
How much longer?
How far is he going?
Sir. I'm almost out of time
for the last train.
Is Musan Station far from here?
How long will it take?
What. Musan Station?
Oh. my. what happened here?
Ambulance...
- Call an ambulance. Now!
- Okay.
Yes. hello. There's been
a vehicle explosion here.
Rest in peace.
I can't tell you to be reborn.
Yul. we're late! Yul. get out!
Yul. what did I say today was?
- Your first day back at work!
- Right?
Then who did I say would pick you up
after daycare today?
Ms. Hee Seon!
Yul. our Yul! Why are you so smart?
Let's go. let's go. Hurry.
Hello. Miss!
Oh. my. Yul is a little late today.
You're starting today. right?
Yes. so starting today.
a helper will be picking Yul up.
But it's our first time.
both for me and Yul. so...
Oh. don't worry too much.
I'll keep a close eye on Yul
and contact you right away
if anything happens.
Thank you.
Yul. My Yul.
- Today. too...
- Today. too. with friends...
Get along well!
See you later.
Have a great day. Ma'am. Let's go in.
Mommy. bye-bye!
[Child on Board]
Okay. let's get going.
Last night. a vehicle exploded on
an outer road in Musan while driving.
The driver. a man in his 40s
identified as Mr. Bae. died at the scene.
Police say they have asked the NFS
to analyze the crash vehicle
and perform an autopsy to determine
the details of the brutal case.
In other news.
Hwang. who had been serving time
for allegedly murdering his pregnant wife.
has been released after three years.
sparking controversy.
Three years ago. Hwang caused
an accident while driving drunk
and was arrested for killing
his pregnant wife in the passenger seat.
What time is it now?
Honey. I missed the last train.
I have some additional reporting to do.
so I think I need to stay here one more day.
I'm sorry.
Just wait till you get home. Kwon Tae Seong.
It's pretty.
[Durumi Electronics]
[Yoo Bo Na]
Excuse me...
What are you doing? Aren't you going in?
Oh. this is so old.
Excuse...
I opened it temporarily for one day.
You can get your new ID badge later.
Pretty good.
Ki Yeong Do. it's been a while.
I'm Assistant Manager Ki.
- What?
- It's been a while since I got promoted.
You got promoted?
Congratulations. Assistant Manager Ki.
You look great.
You haven't changed a bit either.
Really? I couldn't sleep last night.
Why couldn't you sleep?
- Because I heard you were coming back.
- Here it is.
Let's go!
Welcome back!
[Welcome Back. Director Yoo Bo Na]
You're finally back.
Our Director Yoo Bo Na.
whom I've only heard about.
Thank you.
This is Assistant Manager Yang Ye Sol.
who joined while you were away.
She took over from Jeong In Joo.
I've heard so much about you.
I heard you used to be the best on our team.
I've seriously been waiting forever
to meet you.
Not because of your performance or anything.
Anyway. it's really great
to finally meet you.
It's so good to meet you too.
Manager Go. you've been
doing well too. right?
Oh. yeah.
You're finally back. Director Yoo.
I'll head to my desk.
Is the team leader not here yet?
Oh. he went on a business trip
to Musan yesterday.
He got back early this morning.
so he'll be a little late.
Musan?
Oh. I see.
Is he still the same?
Still the same.
You're here?
- You're here?
- Hi! Good morning!
You swept the market again. huh?
What is it this time. Team Leader?
Lettuce. Look how fresh it is.
Ms. Yoo Bo Na is here.
What?
Director Yoo!
Wow. how long has it been?
You're finally back! Our team's ace.
Have you been well?
You're still the same. Team Leader.
Wow. with Director Yoo back.
the office feels full and lively.
A person needs to have some presence.
Oh. right. We'll catch up properly
when we have the time and money.
But today. I have something
urgent on my mind.
Welcome back.
Alright. get back to work!
[Musan City Police Station]
[A Safe. Clean Sea of Hope]
Excuse me. excuse me!
I heard you were at the scene.
May I have your name?
Oh. yes. Just a moment.
I'm Kwon Tae Seong. a reporter
from Digging Deep News. Not Today.
[Not Today Reporter. Kwon Tae Seong]
What's your name. sir?
Well. what brings an investigative reporter
all the way from Seoul to Musan?
Has the victim's identity been confirmed yet?
What on earth is going on here?
I think that's something
I should be asking you.
So what exactly happened here?
Excuse me?
Well. the taxi driver said
you came out of a club
and suddenly asked him to follow this car.
So. what was that about?
Well. what else would a reporter be doing?
I was covering a story.
Like I am now.
A story? What kind of story?
We received information that a new type
of drug had infiltrated clubs around Musan.
So I was meeting an informant today
for an interview. when...
Oh. then what about the car?
Why did you follow it?
Am I a witness? A person of interest?
Or am I a suspect?
No. it's not like that.
Just tell me what happened...
The informant said that man was a dropper.
- A dropper?
- I was following him
in case I could catch him
distributing drugs to other clubs.
Drug-related reports
tend to focus sensationally
on ordinary users consuming drugs.
But I wanted to focus on the suppliers
and expose how these drugs are distributed.
I thought it could raise public awareness
and also help your investigations
and arrests in making society safer.
Does that answer your question?
Oh. yeah. That's admirable.
But if he's a dropper. isn't he just
a low-level errand boy who delivers drugs?
Oh. dear. Mr. Reporter.
I guess you've got the wrong idea.
- Pardon?
- For now. go home.
We may contact you later
for a witness interview.
so please be aware of that.
As you can see.
the scene is a mess right now. I'm off.
Please make sure you take
thorough photos of the scene.
[Son Seok Gu]
- Hello...
- Why do you keep calling?
You're putting me in a difficult position.
I've called you several times.
Why haven't you answered?
I need to see you right now. Where are you?
Meet? What for? It's chaos here
because of what happened.
Don't contact me again.
I'm changing my number.
Wait. hold on! Let me ask you just one thing.
What happened to that dropper from yesterday?
Why are you asking about him?
He came back shortly
after you left yesterday.
- Well. then...
- I'm hanging up.
Hello...
That persistent guy actually showed up.
I told you over the phone
several times that it's not possible.
Who was the victim in last night's incident?
Jeez. what kind of reporter is so pushy...
I'm the one who witnessed
the scene firsthand. Look at me.
I still feel sick to my stomach.
Well. if you feel sick. you can go to
a pharmacy and get some medicine.
I even betrayed my wife.
I was supposed to get home
no matter what yesterday.
Then hurry home now.
Come on. it's already too late.
Today was my wife's first day back at work.
Sir. are you married? My daughter is four.
Why are you telling me
your daughter is four right now?
I mean. it's not really relevant...
Anyway. the victim. Mr. Bae.
is the drug kingpin Bae Doo Hyuk. right?
Well. that's true. but...
Come on.
Was this just an accident?
Or... was it possibly murder?
Come out.
- Is that right?
- Come out!
Please just tell me once.
I said come out. Come out.
- Well. Director Yoo.
- Yes?
I feel bad asking this
on your first day back.
but today. could you do a client meeting?
Today. right away?
Yeah. today.
I know it's a lot to ask on your first day.
And I know you're not someone
who does things halfway.
But the client said today is
the only time they can make it.
Assistant Manager Ki prepared everything.
You just need to handle the meeting.
[Client Report]
You prepared everything thoroughly.
I learned well from you.
Let's do it during the day.
During the day? Why?
Considering the meeting location
and the client's schedule.
having thought about it in detail.
do you think it's strategically better
to do it during the day. Director Yoo?
I have to pick up my kid.
My husband is going to be late today.
Let's do it during the day.
[Client Information]
Whether it's an accident or murder.
we'll know after the NFS results come out.
And I wasn't the one who told you
the victim's name. okay?
[A Safe. Clean Sea of Hope]
Please take me to
the Musan Forensic Science Institute.
I like the meeting venue.
The client arrived an hour ago
and is waiting inside.
You can go right in.
Okay. let's see what you've got.
Me?
Oh. come on. Of course. I...
Not you. me.
Are you nervous?
Well. I guess it has been a while.
That's true for you.
Stop shaking your leg.
You too. Team Leader. Relax your grip.
[Please Hear Our Prayer]
Have you ever prayed?
Of course not. What about you?
Sometimes. without realizing it.
during moments that really shake me.
You have moments like that too? When?
When the child is chewing on
something and eating.
Isn't it a good thing if the child eats well?
The problem is that I never gave
the child anything to eat.
Nothing has ever scared me
more than that moment.
You should see a long bench
in the right corner.
Yeah. I see it.
Do you know when it's hardest
to comfort a crying four-year-old?
- When?
- When a friend gets hurt at daycare.
Oh. out of sadness?
No. guilt. She thought
it was her fault and cried for an hour.
Come on. what does a four-year-old even know?
They know. Even four-year-olds.
What?
They know that they shouldn't
hurt someone. even by accident.
Okay. shall we go?
Now is a good time.
Sales Team 3. Yoo Bo Na.
starting client meeting.
Meeting concluded.
Still got it.
Rest in peace.
I can't tell you to be reborn.
Yoo Bo Na comes back.
- Yul.
- Mommy!
Yul!
- Chae Won. hello.
- Hello.
Did you have fun playing with Chae Won today?
Yeah. I made this with her.
Mommy. it's a present for you!
What is this? Is it a rose?
Yeah.
But it's not my birthday today.
I told her you had a hard first day
back at work. and she made this.
Oh. you did that. Yul?
You like flowers.
Yes. that's right! You're the best. Yul.
My Yul is the best! Thank you.
Let me see. Yul. It looks just like you.
Oh. you're so cute.
Thank you!
Let's go home now. okay?
What concept is this supposed to be?
It's the kind of face you talk about
when you say someone has no shame.
It's not funny at all. Stop it.
Honey. I'm sorry...
I'll go without soup for a month.
I think I can handle it.
Will that be enough?
Not enough?
I'm really sorry.
What exactly are you sorry for?
I mean. I really was going to come home.
even if it was late. but...
Oh. is that all you have to say?
I was going to come home
no matter how late it was.
I even booked the last train ticket.
How could you do this to me?
That's how reporting is. you know.
Once a story breaks.
one thing leads to another.
and it just keeps snowballing...
How could you only buy something for Yul?
What?
Yul. you can only have two. No more. okay?
How could you only buy
the cream-flavored walnut cakes?
You like red bean filling. right?
I really do.
Ever since we first met
about seven years ago.
I think I've only eaten red bean bread.
red bean porridge. and red bean noodles...
Did you already forget that?
I remember.
But how could you...
Yul. put that down.
No. you can't have more than two.
Eat it after dinner.
Okay.
But how could you...
This is the mouth that has no excuses.
- You laughed!
- No. I didn't.
Huh? You laughed.
You laughed! It's over when you smile.
Yul. Mommy laughed!
I'm letting it slide because of Yul. okay?
I'm letting it go because Yul
helped make things easier for me.
Yeah.
Yul did that? Did you help Mommy
even for Daddy's sake?
Oh. my. so cute!
No. wash your hands before touching her.
Yul already took a bath.
I won't touch her. I'll just hug her.
You're my precious treasure.
Right. how was your first day back at work?
After such a long time...
Yul. let's eat after dinner.
- You'll get scolded by Mommy.
- Well. everyone helped me out.
Still. it's something I've done for
a long time. so it came back quickly.
I knew you'd do great. I told you. right?
You'd get back into
the swing of things quickly.
Honey. go wash up quickly. We need to eat.
No. you're tired.
Let's just make do with this today.
Sure. if you say so.
But it's still samgyetang.
Samgyetang?
Yul. she says it's samgyetang.
I will go wash up quickly. okay?
The tenant from Tae Seong Chicken
on the first floor
wanted to visit and greet you in person.
but I declined on your behalf.
But they want to send you a gift.
What should I do?
Honey. can you get me a towel?
Yeah. hold on!
Please politely decline.
And I'll also freeze the rent for next month.
- Thank you for the meal!
- Eat plenty.
Yul. try this.
- Is it good?
- Yeah.
It's super. super good!
Super. super good?
But Yul. didn't you miss Daddy?
- I missed you!
- How much?
This much!
You missed him this much?
Dance as much as you enjoy the food!
[Ok's Flower Shop]
You're early! Did you change your schedule?
Well. right. You have to go to work now.
Why did you open so early?
The sun isn't even up yet.
I need to catch customers on their way
to work. Making a living is tough.
I thought you'd finally have some free time
after sending your kid to daycare.
How does it feel to be back?
My life is about to get a lot busier.
And the world will get noisier. huh?
What flower is this? Is it cosmos?
It's a marguerite.
Oh. marguerite.
Its flower meanings are
"revealing secrets" and "true love."
Come to think of it. this one flower
contains both "secret" and "truth."
"A truthful person has no secrets."
"True love means revealing your secrets."
Is that what it means?
Well. I don't really like that meaning.
Sometimes you keep secrets
because you love someone too much.
Aren't you worried that
the day might come
when your husband finds out?
Well. the night before I went back to work.
my husband promised he'd come home early.
but then he suddenly had to go out of town.
He said he'd come home
even if it was late. but he never did.
Oh. dear.
I knew it was because of his reporting.
but I was still hurt.
I was busy getting ready.
but I just got upset for no reason.
"Kwon Tae Seong. just you wait
till you get home tonight."
There I was. all fired up by myself.
and then I just ended up laughing.
I found myself so strange and amazing.
And I still can't believe moments like that.
I love them.
So I'm not worried.
Because that day will never come.
He's someone who lives in the light.
Because he's different from me.
Because if he knew how different we are.
we couldn't stay together.
You don't really know much about me. do you?
I don't know much about you. Bo Na.
I know your name. but...
I don't even know if it's your real name.
Where you were born. how you grew up...
What your family is like.
or what you do for a living...
Why you were standing there
- on the day we first met?
- Hold on!
- Come down. now!
- I don't know those things either.
Oh. slowly!
But I do know some aspects of you. Bo Na.
Perhaps love begins...
when you find yourself drawn to
just one side of a person
among all the many sides they have.
I've already fallen in love.
My name is Yoo Bo Na. It's my real name.
Please take care of me.
It's my first time with love.
I'm not worried.
Because that day will never come.
Because the day he sees
my other side will never come.
Breaking news.
A shooting using a sniper rifle
has occurred in the heart of Seoul.
Some speculate that Kingfisher.
the infamous serial gun killer
[Breaking News: Kingfisher Returns?]
who disappeared for the past four years.
[Shooting Homicide in Seoul]
may have returned.
The incident took place at a hotel
in Jeonjak-dong. Seoul.
A man in his thirties.
identified as Mr. Hwang.
was struck and killed by a bullet
fired from outside the building.
For more details. we'll soon connect live to
our reporter on the scene
for the latest on the police investigation...
[A Bona Fide Killer]
A gun murder in South Korea?
I think that punk is back.
From now on. you're going
after Kingfisher. right?
I'll really give it my all this time.
Is it really the Kingfisher?
[Musan Drug Kingpin's Car Explosion]
You're covering the Kingfisher story. right?
Like. you find anything at the shooting site.
Did you come here knowing something?
Hey. you never know.
What if that was the real clue?
[I'd like to provide a tip about Kingfisher]
But sometimes.
[Security Alert]
I think that day might actually come.
He might find me.
Shall I schedule a meeting?
Don't you think something's strange?
[Yoo Bo Na. Husband. Company]
Honestly. a guy like him
getting gunned down
by the Kingfisher is just unsurprising.
What would you do if you lost
the things that matter most to you?
Where's Kwon Tae Seong?
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today